https://www.dnatechindia.com/privacy.html

My Account
Register
Login
Wish List (0)
Shopping Cart
Checkout
Attention !!!
We are shipping orders now but due to Covid-19 situation it can take 1-2 days for your orders to be shipped from our Nashik warehouse. If you have any queries feel free to contact us. Thank you for your support and understanding.
Menu
Home
Projects
Ready Projects
Project List
Synopsis and Abstract
Show All Projects
Tutorial
Samsung 18650 2600mah Li-ion Battery
Samsung ICR18650-26J 2.6Ah BatteryOriginal Samsung 18650 2600 mah Lithium-ion BatteryThis is or..
Rs.247.80
(inc GST)
Rs.210.00 + GST
SKU: 1183 | DAB424
Stock:
0
Add to Cart
Arduino Mega 2560 Pro Mini
Mega Pro 2560 Development Board Mega 2560 Pro a  Atmega2560 based compact Arduino MegaThis..
Rs.794.66
(inc GST)
Rs.673.44 + GST
SKU: 2058 | DAB079
Stock:
13
Add to Cart
Other Products
AM2302 Humidity And Temperature Module
AM2302 Sensor ModuleAM2302 Temperature and Humidity Sensor Module (wired DHT22 Sensor)The AM2302 is ..
Rs.482.38
(inc GST)
Rs.408.80 + GST
SKU: 2083 | DAB080
Stock:
5
Write review
Add to Cart
1206 SMD Yellow LED (PACK of 10)
SMD Yellow LED 1206 Package (PACK of 10)
Yellow SMD LED in 1206 PackageNow a days hobbyist an..
Rs.18.88
(inc GST)
Rs.16.00 + GST
SKU: 1494 | DAB663
Stock:
50
Write review
Add to Cart
ZERO PCB 13X25 SINGLE SIDED PAPER PHENOLIC
General Purpose 13X25 SINGLE SIDED PAPER PHENOLIC PCBGeneral Purpose 13cm x 25cm dotted SINGLE SIDED..
Rs.113.28
(inc GST)
Rs.96.00 + GST
SKU: 2118 | DAB896
Stock:
32
Write review
Add to Cart
Privacy Policy
DNA Technology value's the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We also respect the users privacy and do not take any personal information without users permission.DNA Technology assumes the following responsibilities:Protecting all data generated by and provided to us by our users from being stolen, compromised, or used in violation with this policy.Never selling user-provided and user-generated data for financial gain or competitive advantage.Your sensitive information is never shared, rented or sold to a third party. What Information do we collect?If you register an account with DNA Technology, we’ll have access to your e-mail address and any additional contact information you choose to provide us. If you place an order, we retain a record of the contents of the order, delivery and billing address information, and any communication you might have us. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.Cookies and HTTPSTo improve your online experience with DNA Technology, the majority of our pages use "cookies". These cookies can in no way divulge personal information and can not be used to deliver or activate a virus. The cookies provide us vital information on navigation, purchase statistics, entry and exit pages on our website, origins of user traffic, etc. This information allows DNA Technology to optimize our internet activities to better serve you.Links To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Email AddressWhen you place an order at DNA Technology, your email address is also collected in order to send you a copy of your invoice and a tracking number during delivery of your purchase. This email address is also conserved in our database in order to serve you better. If you register for the DNA Technology newsletter, your email will also be used to send you the monthly DNA Technology news. You can always unregister by simply clicking on a link of the newsletter.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the form in contact us page.
No Noise(spam) only Information
Get In Touch
Shop:
FH11-12, Thakker Bazar,
NEW CBS, Nashik 422002,
Maharashtra, India
8412906903
dnatechindia@gmail.com
PAYMENT
DNA Technology is an Online shop for Electronic Components located in Nashik, Maharashtra and delivering Electronic Components all across India. DNA Solutions now has great collection of MOSFET & IGBT, Relimate Connectors and Heat Shrink Sleeve as well. List of some of cities we have dispatched to:
shivaji Nagar
Namrup
Thane
Pilani
Ballia
Darbhanga
Kannur
Junagadh
Copyright © 2015 DNA TECHNOLOGY, INDIA . All Rights Reserved.
